all Russians want to discuss Ukraine no The
все россияне хотят обсуждать Украину нет
time has come for the collapse of the Russian
Пришло время распада Российской
Federation the whole world is now discussing the
Федерации весь мир теперь обсуждает
collapse of the Russian
распад Российской
Federation What are you discussing here like this I am discussing
Федерации Что обсуждаете здесь так
today the prospects for the collapse of the
обсуждаю вот сегодня перспективы распада
Russian Federation Perhaps this is
Российской Федерации Возможно это
impossible I communicate with people like this
невозможно вот так общаюсь с людьми вы
What
из какого
region are you from I said Krasnoyarsk Territory
региона Я же сказал Красноярский край
Krasnoyarsk Territory I understand  look, you can
Красноярского края Поня вот смотрите Вы
hear me on the other side,
по ту сторону слышно меня
yes, yes, it’s me who
да да это я второй телефон
turned on the second phone. Why will it be
включил Зачем будет
audible Damn, well, now I’m losing sound there,
слышно Блин ну сейчас я звук там
then then look, look, there
уба потом потом посмотрите смотри там
you can stream the stream, we’ll talk, you’ll come back to this later, the beginning of
вы се потом вернётесь в этот начало
your conversation,
свого разговора
when I came across such a mate on  Stream there,
пори попадал на такое мате на Стрим там
well, today you’re watching your finest hour
ну вот сегодня у вас Звёздный час
You were once on the other side of the Urals,
смотрите Вы когда-то по ту сторону Урала
here in the European part of Russia,
были вот в европейской части России
uh, And in the European part, of course, you
э в как А в европейской части конечно
were Yes, uh, what unites you, a resident of Krasnoyarsk,
был Да вот ээ что вас жителе Красноярска
for example, with the residents of
например объединяет с жителями
Pskov
Пскова
Well,
Ну
what can we
что что нас может
unite citizenship That's it Yes,
объединять гражданство Вот именно Да вот
this is citizenship because you are kept in
это гражданство потому что вас держат в
one country And like this, in addition,
одной стране А вот так кроме кроме того
if you had different
Вот если бы у вас были разные
citizenships, what would
гражданства что бы
change, well, for example, look to the Urals, the
изменилось ну например смотрите до Урала
European part is one country, for example,
европейская часть одна страна например
Siberia, another country, the Far East, a
Сибирь другая страна Дальний Восток
third country.
третья страна
what were the problems Well, we are not
В чём проблемы были Ну мы не
considering this issue, you understand
рассматриваем этот вопрос понимаете
us We are happy with what we have now, so
нам Мы довольны тем что сейчас есть так
yes, I say Look what we have now,
вот да я говорю Смотри что сейчас есть
this is what Moscow, for example, what it takes from
вот что Москва например что берёт от
Krasnoyarsk, we understand the resources, money and
Красноярска мы понимаем ресурсы деньги и
people, and what Moscow gives you in
людей а что Москва даёт вам в
Krasnoyarsk normally gives what  she gives
красноярску нормально даёт что она даёт
you anything the state wants, don’t
вам да всё что угодно госпо не ещё раз
look again, that is, Moscow takes
смотрите то есть Москва забирает у
money and natural resources from Krasnoyarsk
Красноярска деньги ресурсы природные Да
And people, have you ever been to
и людей а вы были когда-нибудь в
Krasnoyarsk now now now I’m
Красноярске сейчас сейчас сейчас я
explaining the question the question is what Krasnoyarsk
объясняю вопрос вопрос что Красноярск
receives in return from
получает взамен от
Moscow and you were once-  somewhere in
Москвы а вы были когда-нибудь в
Krasnoyarsk thank God I wasn’t there were
Красноярске слава Богу не
n’t And why thank God Well,
был не были А почему слава Богу Ну
somehow I don’t want to go there in this cold weather
как-то не хочется туда в эти холода
Well, the cold - This is not the most
ехать в холода Ну холод - Это не самое
important thing, you know, people go to Sweden to
главное понимаете люди ездят в швеца
ski, let’s say yes yes I
покататься на лыжах допустим да да
agree, well, why can you go  Krasnoyarsk
согласен ну ради чего можно в Красноярск
to come This is bad, why is it worth
приехать Это плохо ради чего в
coming to Krasnoyarsk? Have you
Красноярск стоит приехать вы были
ever been to the Yenisei, oh, you
когда-нибудь на Енисее вот о вот на
would have come to the Yenisei and understood everything. I understand, yes,
Енисее бы приехал всё понял Понял да
tourism, you have tourism, that is, yes, of
туризм у вас туризм есть всё су то есть
course, the state has a huge tourist
да конечно гос огромнейший туристический
potential, so the question is: What does Moscow
потенциал так вопрос А что Москва вам
give you?  Yes, a lot What, for example,
даёт Да много Что даёт например
development gives again You are satisfied No I didn’t
развитие ещё раз Вы довольны Нет не
understand what development is at a time You don’t
понял что за раз развитие Вы плохо
understand well What I don’t understand well if
Понимаете в чём плохо понимаю если
Moscow takes money from you, resources and
Москва у вас забирает деньги ресурсы и
people in what to develop Wait stop
людей в чём развити Подождите стоп
Why do you think that they are taking something from us
Почему вы думаете что у нас что-то
I don’t  I think I see, look,
забирают я не думаю я вижу смотрите у
you have tax deductions, where do you see,
вас идут налоговые отчисления откуда
where are you, look, I
видите Вы где находитесь смотрите я
’m in minicom, I open Google and
нахожусь в миником я Я открываю Google и
look, yes, and I look at the deductions, look, I’m
смотрю да и смотрю отчисление смотрите я
not in a hurry again Yandex open, calmly
не спе не сза ещё раз Яндекс откры
open Yandex, look, I see
спокой открываю Яндекс смотрите Я смотрю
that Moscow is taking away the budget is taking away
что Москва забирает бюджет забирает
taxes to the federal budget, that is, to
налоги в федеральный бюджет да то есть в
Moscow, which then she begins to
Москву которые потом она начинает
distribute in her own way. Back you see
расправлять по своему назад вы видите
that what she gives back What What gives I
что что она даёт назад Что Что даёт Я
ask Wait, you see what she
спрашиваю Подождите вы видите что она
takes and what she gives back you
забирает а что она отдаёт назад вы
see look like the question she takes
видите смотрите так вопрос она забирает
for example on X  the ruble gives back to Y
например на X руб отдаёт назад на Y В
Why does Krasnoyarsk need this, why give
чём зачем это красноярску зачем отдавать
money to Moscow so that part of it can only
Москве деньги чтоб часть из них только
be returned
вернуть
to itself for what? Have you ever been to
себе ради чего А Вы были когда-нибудь в
Krasnoyarsk, look again for why
Красноярске смотри ещё раз ради чего
Moscow is giving this difference x and and you
Москва отдаёт эту разницу икса и и вы
Answer the question posed I
Ответьте на поставленный вопрос я
never  I wasn’t
никогда не был
But you
Но
can Then tell me I’m asking you I’m
може Тогда мне сказать Я вас спрашиваю Я
not saying I’m asking I’m asking you how you
же не говорю я спрашиваю я вас как вы
were I’m giving investment You are now in Kra What
были даю инвести Вы сейчас в Кра Какие
investments if she takes the money then
инвестиции если она забирает деньги то
what kind of investments are you investing in
какие инвестиции это вы инвестирует в
Moscow she gives if she
москви отдаёт она если она у вас
takes the money from you and  some of them give away
забирает деньги и часть из них отдаёт
this is not an investment, what are you trying to get from me now?
это не инвестиции вы что от меня сейчас
I want to understand what you
пытаетесь добиться Я хочу понять что вы
get from Moscow, that it wants to
получаете от Москвы то что она ва хоте
understand nothing, I see that you have it.
ничего понять я вижу что она у вас
Let me ask you again, have you
Давайте ещё раз я вам задаю вопрос а вы
ever been to me?  I answered you for the
были когда-нибудь ко я вам ответил
third time, thank God I’ve never been to
третий раз я никогда слава Богу не был в
Krasnoyarsk in Khabarovsk and Khabarovsk
Красноярске в Хабаровске и в Хабаровске
Thank God I’ve never been I haven’t been
Слава Богу я никогда не был не были
Glory and in Omsk [ __ ] God the hut is absolutely
Слава а в Омске бля Боже изба это вообще
crap Yes it’s better to go to Krasnoyarsk
с срань Да лучше в Красноярск съездить А
Why are you discussing this at all then
зачем вы это обсуждаете вообще тогда А
Let’s  let's discuss ki Oh no, that's
давайте обсудим ки О нет вот Вот потому
because we Let's discuss ki No,
что мы Давайте обсудим ки Нет ты среза
you're running away because all Russians
ты убегаешь потому что все россияне
want to discuss Ukraine no The time has come for the
хотят обсуждать Украину нет Пришло время
collapse of the Russian Federation, the whole world is
распада Российской Федерации весь мир
now discussing the collapse of the Russian
теперь обсуждает распад Российской
Federation, I started discussing the collapse of the
Федерации я начал обсуждать распад
Russian Federation and you can't
Российской Федерации и вы не можете
say what to you  Moscow gives see all
сказать что вам даёт Москва смотрите все
residents of
житель
Krasnoyarsk all Russians watch
Красноярска все россияне смотрите
Krasnoyarsk cannot name What
Красноярска не может назвать Что даёт
Moscow gives Krasnoyarsk cannot investment What is
Москва красноярску не может инвестиции В
investment if it takes money
чём инвестиции если оно забирает деньги
What kind of investment is development like
Какие это инвестиции развитие какко
development what does it give
развитие что она даёт
specifically streets road surface houses
конкретно улицы дорожное покрытие дома
For what money for what money are they built
За какие деньги за какие деньги строятся
in Krasnoyarsk  schools roads and kindergartens you
в Красноярске школы дороги и садики вы
Drink water For what kind of money look if
Пите воды За какие деньги смотрите если
Moscow collects money from all regions Yes and
Москва собирает со всех регио Деги Да и
some of them return to the roads Yes and
часть из них возвращает на дороги Да а
some of them are kept for themselves, is it Moscow that
часть оставляет себе то это Москва
is building it or is it being built for your money?
строит или это за ваши деньги
We are building it for ourselves, it is our
строят мы сами себе строим это наше
state, so Moscow  What does it have to do with what you are
государст так Москва Причём тут то
building here? You once again Moscow don’t run away for
строите Вы ещё раз Москва не убегай за
Whose money they build roads in Krasnoyarsk
Чьи деньги строят дороги в Красноярске
say for the common not not for the common That is, they took it from
скажи за общий не не за общий То есть за
you, so look like this,
вас у вас забрали значит смотрите так
the residents of Krasnoyarsk Moscow pays
жители Краснояр Москва платит
taxes to you
налоги вам
about Moscow pays soda, we caught a
об Москва платит натрите мы поймали
resident of Krasnoyarsk who confirmed
жителя Красноярска который подтвердил
that Moscow doesn’t give anything, that Moscow
что Москва не даёт ничего что Москва
takes money from the regions and gives some of
забирает деньги из регионов и часть из
it back, that Moscow gives money, doesn’t give it,
них отдаёт что Москва даёт деньги не
if it gives it,
даёт если если она даёт зачем она
why does it take it? What are you yelling about if Moscow gives money, why does it
деньги зачем она
take it?
забирает
Where do taxes go from the Lviv region,
куда налоги уходят с Львовской области
don’t run away again? No  don’t run away from the topic,
ещё раз не убегай Нет не убегай с темы
don’t see again, watch all the residents of the
не види ещё раз смотрите все жители
Russian Federation, we see how this
Российской Федерации мы видим как этот
person is being cut off. He wants to run away from the
человек срезается Он хочет убежать с
topic because we have proven that Moscow
темы потому что мы доказали что Москва
gives nothing to Krasnoyarsk because
ничего не даёт красноярску потому что
it takes everything, it only takes away
она забирает всё она забирает только и
some of it and gives it away like a dacha  from the
часть из этого даёт как по дачку с
Barsky shoulder super you're yelling You
Барского плеча супер ты орёшь Вы
confirmed look you're yelling fire m spa
подтвердили смотрите ты орёшь огне м спа
blogger You confirmed I consider myself a
блогером Вы подтвердили Я считаю себя
kick-ass blogger Yes I just
офигительный блогером Да я
confirmed in person you see you
сейчас наочно подтвердил видите вы
got burned because the residents of Krasnoyarsk
подгорели потому что жители Красноярска
Vladivostok Omsk is separating from the
Владивостока Омска отделяется с от
Russian Federation Stop paying
Российской Федерации Хватит платить
taxes to Moscow Moscow is taking it from you
налоги в Москву Москва забирает у вас
you don’t hear money, resources and people for your imperial ambitions,
амбиций ты не слышишь
but She considers you as slaves who need to be
а вас Она считает за рабов которых нужно
torn from them, money to be torn from them, life torn from them.
выдирать из них деньги выдирать из них
You live in poverty,
жизнь Вы живёте в бедности вам даёт
Moscow gives you some kind of allowance for the road and you
Москва какую-то подач на дорогу и вы
say Moscow builds roads for us. Moscow
говорите Москва нам строит дороги Москва
gives it to us.  if Moscow gives, why does it
нам даёт если Москва даёт зачем она
take away? Because the Bible also says that
забирает потому что ещё в Библии сказано
it is not the one who takes away who gives. Come on. If you
даёт не тот кто забирает Давай м Если ты
don’t want to communicate with me as with your
не хочешь со мной обща как со своим
person. Well, who did you get in touch with? Well,
человеком Ну с кем ты вышел на связь Ну
talk, let’s put up a mirror and talk to
говори давай поставь зеркало и говори с
him, you don’t talk to me  you want to talk like that, you
ним ты со мной не хочешь говорить так ты
can’t
не можешь
say it again, let’s calm down and
сказать ещё раз давай успокойся и скажи
just tell me what Moscow is giving you,
просто че что вам даёт Москва я ж у тебя
I’m asking you, that’s where I started, I
спрашиваю я с этого и начал я с тобой
started communicating with you, I want you to
начал общаться Я хочу чтобы ты мне
answer me, what is Moscow giving to Krasnoyarsk,
ответил Что даёт Москва красноярску
tell me what kind of obscenities are you
говори каком матом это ты
swearing?  those are not the uterus,
матюка те не матка ни слова матом не
I didn’t say a word, I didn’t say a word atom Speak
сказал Я ни слово атом не сказал Говори
answer What Moscow gives to
отвечай Что Москва даёт
Krasnoyarsk you will answer or not there is nothing to
красноярску ответишь или нет нечего
answer look all the people of the Russian
ответить смотрите все люди Российской
Federation the dude
Федерации чувак
ran away like comment squeak like this residents of the
убежал лайк коммент писка вот так жители
Russian Federation We see once again
Российской Федерации Мы ещё раз видим
Moscow does not give anything to the
Москва не даёт ничего региона
Moscow region  if it takes away and then
Москва если забирает а потом часть
gives part of it back, it’s not Moscow that gives it, Moscow
отдаёт это не Москва даёт это Москва у
took it from you and then threw you a dacha from the
вас забрала а потом кинула по дачку с
Barsky shoulder, only real
Барского плеча только реальная
independence will lead you to freedom and
независимость приведёт к вас к свободе и
prosperity, subscribe to th Telegram directly at
процветанию подпишись на й Telegram прям
once, the VN
зараз ось ВН
axis apok tse more and more
апок це дуже и дуже
respectfully
важливо